[
  {
    "prompt": "At what BAC do most people start to show slowed reaction time?",
    "choices": ["0.02", "0.05", "0.08"],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the legal BAC limit for driving in most US states?",
    "choices": ["0.04", "0.08", "0.10"],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Alcohol affects which of the following first?",
    "choices": ["Motor skills", "Judgment", "Balance"],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which age group receives the most DUIs?",
    "choices": ["30-33", "25-29", "21-24"],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do men or women receive more DUIs?",
    "choices": ["Men", "Women", "Neither, it's about equal"],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What percent of all US traffic fatalities involve an impaired driver?",
    "choices": ["10%", "30%", "50%"],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How much on average does a DUI conviction cost including legal fees?",
    "choices": ["$1,000", "$5,000", "$10,000"],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How many people die in the US from alcohol related crashes in the US every day?",
    "choices": ["8", "19", "27"],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What fraction of Americans will be involved in a drunk driving crash in their lifetime?",
    "choices": ["1/5", "1/3", "2/3"],
    "answer": 2
  },
    {
    "prompt": "What will help you sober up after drinking alcohol?",
    "choices": ["Coffee", "Time", "Carbohydrates"],
    "answer": 1
  }
]